<resources>
    <array name="relation">
        <item>Mother</item>
        <item>Father</item>
        <item>Brother</item>
        <item>Sister</item>
        <item>Uncle</item>
        <item>Son</item>
        <item>Daughter</item>
        <item>Wife</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </array>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">1845017522768855</string>
    <string name="at_sign">\@</string>
    <!-- Navigation Drawer menu labels -->
    <array name="occasion">
        <item>Architeccture &amp; Interiors</item>
        <item>Automobile</item>
        <item>Bakery</item>
        <item>Day Care</item>
        <item>Education</item>
        <item>Entertainment and Media</item>
        <item>Fruits &amp; Vegetables</item>
        <item>Garments</item>
    </array>
    <!--<string name="facebook_app_id">929962769257001</string>-->
<!--    <string name="facebook_client_token">d5492151458f6c35a3177b9ea03e0c29</string>-->
  <string name="facebook_client_token">541363f552e157ebd238d3d82612a88d</string>

    <string name="app_name">Neighbrsnook</string>
    <string name="nav_home">Home</string>
    <string name="nav_photos">Photos</string>
    <string name="nav_movies">Movies</string>
    <string name="nav_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="nav_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="nav_about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="address_line_1">Flat/House no, Apartment name</string>
    <string name="address_line_2">Road/Street name</string>
    <string name="provide_contact_details">Business address</string>
    <!-- Toolbar titles when navigation menu item is selected -->
    <string name="state">State</string>
    <string name="show"> less</string>
    <string name="less">....more</string>
    <string name="back"><![CDATA[<-]]></string>
    <string name="forward"><![CDATA[->]]></string>
    <string name="terms_condition">This End-User
        License Agreement ("EULA") is a legal agreement between the end user ("you") and Neighbrsnook Private Limited ("Company name"),
        the owner of intellectual property rights in this software "[Neighbrsnook]" ("App").
By installing the software, or otherwise using all or any portion of App, or clicking/ticking on the "I ACCEPT" button next to
        EULA link during registration, you agree that this EULA, like any other written negotiated agreement is signed by you and is
        binding on you. This EULA is enforceable against you. This EULA is an electronic record in terms of the Information Technology
        Act, 2000 and Rules made thereunder. This electronic record is generated by a computer system and does not require any physical
        or digital signatures.
The App is owned by Neighbrsnook Private Limited ("Company name"),
        a company incorporated under the Companies Act, 2013 located at India. This App is a communication tool
        that enables users of the App to communicate and exchange messages by way of a social platform within your neighbourhoods.
        Users can share images, video and messages ("Data") in various forms through the App. </string>
    <string name="p1">Neighbrsnook is extremely serious about protecting your privacy and we invite you to read this privacy policy, which explains our privacy practices and how we treat your information.
The app and website are published and maintained by Neighbrsnook Private Limited, headquartered in India.	The Privacy Policy is applicable to the website of Neighbrsnook (www.neighbrsnook.com), and also comprises of the mobile site Smartphone App Platforms such as iOS, Android (all
together referred to as	(“ Site ” ).This privacy policy does not apply to the websites of our business partners, corporate affiliates or to any other third parties, even if their websites may have been linked to the
site. We recommend you to review the respective privacy statements of the other parties with whom you interact. By browsing, visiting, accessing and/or using the services on this Site
(or searching for any of the pages on this Site), the member explicitly consents and agrees to our Privacy Policy laid out herein. You also agree that the information furnished by you is lawful, true and correct	and does not violate or infringe	any laws. In case of any violations,	infringement, furnishing	of wrongful	or unauthorized information, Neighbrsnook shall not be liable for the same. We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy, and familiarise with it.Please note that we review our Privacy Policy from time to time, and we may make periodic changes to the policy in connection with that review. Therefore, you may wish to visit this page and/or from time to time and review to make sure you have the updated version of the Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="permission_needed">Camera permission needed. Please allow in App Settings for additional functionality</string>
    <string name="grant_permission">In order to use App, you must first agree to the EULA. By accessing or using App, you are agreeing to the terms contained in this EULA and concluding a legally binding contract with Company name.
You may not use App if you do not accept the terms of this EULA or are unable to be bound by this EULA.
        Your use of App and services and tools are governed by this EULA and shall include the applicable policies which are incorporated herein by way of reference.
As a condition of your access to and use of App, you agree that you will comply with all
        applicable laws and regulations when using App.
Company name reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to change, modify, add or remove all or any part of this EULA, at
        any time without any prior notice to you. It is your sole responsibility to review this EULA periodically for updates or
        changes. Your continued use of the App following the posting of changes shall be deemed to mean that you accept and agree to
        the revisions. As long as you comply with this EULA, Company name grants you a non-exclusive, non-transferable, limited license,
        to use the App.
 You acknowledge and agree that all the rights, title and interest in App and all the intellectual
        property rights therein are solely and absolutely owned by Company name and shall continue to vest with Company name during the use of App by you as per the terms and conditions of this EULA. Nothing herein provides you with any right, title or interest in App or any intellectual property rights therein.</string>

    <string name="thanks_neighbrsnook">Thank you for choosing Neighbrsnook. Your account will be up and running after a quick verification.We welcome you to browse around!
    </string>

    <string name="subscription">Use of the App is available only to persons who can enter into legally binding
        contracts under the Indian Contract Act, 1872. Persons who are incompetent to contract within the meaning of the Indian
        Contract Act, 1872 including un-discharged insolvents and persons of unsound mind are not eligible to use the App. Company
        name reserves the right to terminate any person’s membership and/or refuse to provide such person with access to the App if
        it is brought to Company name’s notice or if it is discovered that such person is not eligible to use the App.
Further you agree that you shall be liable for all charges incurred for use of the App on your mobile device,
        including without limitation, download, streaming and subscription charges, data and airtime charges,
        standard and premium messaging charges and any other charges that may be incurred using the mobile device,
        including any such charges incurred by any third party that accesses your mobile device.</string>
    <string name="opening_an_account">In order to use Company name s communication tool for sending messages ("Services") on the App,
        you will have to create an account on the App ("Account"), which can be done through your email, and mobile number.
        As a part of the registration process, you will be required to provide certain information and details, including your name,
        your mobile number, an e-mail id, gender, age, date of birth, address and any other information deemed necessary by Company
        name. You hereby acknowledge that you will be fully responsible for all activities that occur under your Account.
You shall be responsible for maintaining the confidentiality and security of the password and for all activities that occur in and
        through your Account. Company name and its affiliates / partners / associates/ officers/ directors/ agents/ subsidiaries/
        joint ventures and/or employees are not liable for any kind of harm or damages  caused by or related to the theft of your IDs,
        disclosure of your Account / account information by you or any of your employees (as may be applicable), or your authorization
        to allow another person (other than the authorized employee, if applicable) to access and use App using your Account. However,
        you may be liable to Company name and its affiliates / partners/ associates/ officers/ directors/ agents/ and/or employees for
        the losses caused to them due to such unauthorized use. In case you notice any misappropriation or unauthorized access of your
        Account, you agree to communicate the same promptly to Company name against which Company name shall take earliest appropriate
        action and any response from Company name regarding this will be sent to the e-mail address which was used by you at the time
        of sign up.
You shall ensure that the account information provided by you is complete, accurate and up-to-date. In case you wish to update or
        correct the information provided by you, you may do so by visiting My profile to update your account details section on App.
Use of another user’s account information for availing the Services of App is expressly prohibited.
You hereby agree that if you provide any information that is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete, (or becomes untrue,
        inaccurate, not current or incomplete)or if Company name has reasonable grounds to suspect that such information is untrue,
        inaccurate, not current, incomplete, or not in accordance with this EULA, Company name shall have the right to indefinitely
        suspend or terminate or block access of your membership on App and refuse to provide you with access to App.</string>
    <string name="subscriptions">While you may continue to use most features of App free of cost "i.e."
        without making any payments towards subscriptions. There may be some features which can be used only
        after payment for
        relevant charges
        from the time period agreed with the Company name.</string>
    <string name="payment_terms">You hereby agree that you shall be liable for all fees and charges associated with your use of
        specific sections of App and Company name’s Services like Advertisement. We may charge you for provision of those Services,
        including applicable taxes. Payments made to Company name for the Services shall be non-refundable under all circumstances.
All payments made for the use of App by you shall be in Indian Rupees.
You acknowledge that Company name will not be liable for any damages, interests or claims, losses resulting from or suffered on
        account of not processing a transaction/ transaction amount or any delay in processing a transaction/ transaction amount
        which is beyond the control of Company name.
Company name holds the authority to temporarily/permanently suspend/terminate your Account or refuse access in case of non-payment
        of fees due by you to Company name. Company name also reserves the right to take legal action for the same.

</string>
    <string name="nature_service">This End-User License Agreement (“EULA”) is a legal agreement between the end user (“you”) and Neighbrsnook Private Limited ("Company name"), the owner of intellectual property rights in this software “[Neighbrsnook]” (“App”).
By installing the software, or otherwise using all or any portion of the App, you agree that this EULA, like any other written negotiated agreement, is signed by you and is binding on you. This EULA is enforceable against you. This EULA is an electronic record in terms of the Information Technology Act, 2000 and Rules made thereunder. This electronic record is generated by a computer system and does not require any physical or digital signatures.
The App is owned by Neighbrsnook Private Limited (“Company name”), a company incorporated under the Companies Act, 2013 located in India. This App is a communication tool that enables users of the App to communicate and exchange messages by way of a social platform within your neighbourhoods. Users can share images, videos, and messages (“Data”) in various forms through the App.</string>

    <string name="permission">In order to use the App on your mobile handset, the App shall require permission to access your camera,
        photos and videos, storage, location, contacts and permission to access third party applications.
        You agree that you shall provide the aforementioned permissions in order to use all the features on the App.</string>
    <string name="use_of_the_app">You agree, undertake and covenant that, during the use of the App,you shall not host, display, upload, transmit or share any information that.</string>
    <string name="point_one">Belongs to another person or entity and to which you do not have any right.</string>
    <string name="point_two">Is grossly harmful, harassing, blasphemous, defamatory, obscene, pornographic,
        pedophilic, libelous, invasive of another persons privacy, hateful or racially or ethnically objectionable, or
        encouraging money laundering or gambling, or otherwise unlawful in any manner whatsoever</string>
    <string name="point_four">Involves the transmission of junk mail, chain letters, or unsolicited mass mailing or spamming.</string>

    <string name="point_five">Infringes upon or violates any third partys rights including, but not limited to, intellectual property rights, rights of privacy (including without
         limitation unauthorized disclosure of a persons name e-mail address physical address or phone number) or rights of publicity.</string>
    <string name="point_six">provides instructional information about illegal activities such as violating someone privacy or providing or creating computer viruses.</string>
    <string name="points_saven">Tries to gain unauthorized access or exceeds the scope of authorized access to the App or to profiles,
        blogs, communities, account information, bulletins, or other areas of the
        App or solicits passwords or personally identifying information for commercial or unlawful purposes from other users of the App.</string>
    <string name="points_eight">Engages in commercial activities without Company names prior written consent such as engages in
        sweepstakes, barter, etc.
</string>
    <string name="points_ten">refers to any website or URL that, in Company names sole discretion, contains material that is
        inappropriate for the App or any other mobile application, contains content that would be prohibited or violates the letter or
        spirit of this EULA.
</string>
    <string name="points_eleven">Deceives or misleads the addressee/ users about the origin of such messages or communicates any
        information which is grossly offensive or menacing in nature.
</string>
    <string name="points_twelve">Contains software viruses or any other computer codes, files or programs designed to interrupt,
        destroy or limit the functionality of any computer resource; or contains any trojan horses, worms or other computer programming
        routines that may damage, detrimentally interfere with,
        diminish value of, covertly intercept or steal any system, data or personal information.</string>

    <string name="t1">Personally Identifiable Information like name(s) and contact details which may include e-mail address or contact number(s), password, address etc. when you register for Neighbrsnook.</string>

    <string name="t2">Suggestions or recommendations or rating about local business</string>
    <string name="t4">Your posts when you want to communicate with your neighbours and share Content. Other information that may be requested or gathered while you visit, access or use the Site. Besides the above, when you browse the Website, Neighbrsnook may
collect	information	regarding	the domain	and host from which you access the Internet, the Internet Protocol address of the computer Internet Service Provider you are using, and anonymous site statistical
data, information furnished while navigating the Site, the systems
        and programs used and the time spent on our Site along with any other relevant information.
        The Website uses cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered</string>
    <string name="t3">Information about yourself in your profile like your interests etc to help your neighbours get to know you better so you can exchange information related to your interests</string>
    <string name="t5">We may also collect and furnish such other information as is required in compliance	of various	laws, court order, as requested	by other
government or law enforcement authority, or in the good faith believe that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable including, without
limitation, to protect the rights or properties of Neighbrsnook or any or all of its affiliates, associates, employees, directors or officers or when
we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be
causing	interference	to our operations	rights,	interests,	whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed b such activities.
We may retain your information in our server logs, and our databases for as long as necessary in light of the purposes set out in this Policy,
subject to any legal obligations to further retain such information. We may retain your verification-related information for a reasonable period of time,</string>
    <string name="city">City</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="title_activity_maps">MapsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_2">Activity2</string>
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>

    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="title_activity_report">ReportActivity</string>
    <string name="resend_otp">RESEND OTP</string>
    <string name="title_activity_real_state_landmark">RealStateLandmark</string>
    <string name="_20b9">20B9</string>
<!--    <string name="api_key">AIzaSyAvgQuGAFU2BVsCw1npCeZKC_roTM5HUHs</string>-->
    <string name="api_key">AIzaSyAnDzn9U5yUu9OqSXxnTr7hXdWEN9VMOSE</string>
    <string-array name="nav_item_activity_titles">
        <item>Home</item>
        <item>Photos</item>
        <item>Movies</item>
        <item>Notifications</item>
        <item>Settings</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="my_text"><u>underline</u>.</string>
    <string name="unverified_user_msg">Your registration is almost complete and pending for just a verification. Till that period you have limited access.</string>
    <string name="unverified_msg">You have limited access till verification is complete. We thank you for your patience.</string>
    <string name="abusive_msg">
   This post goes against our community guidelines.Please keep things respectful.
</string>
    <string name="title_activity_post">PostActivity</string>
    <string name="lorem_ipsum">
        Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Nam in scelerisque sem. Mauris
        volutpat, dolor id interdum ullamcorper, risus dolor egestas lectus, sit amet mattis purus
        dui nec risus. Maecenas non sodales nisi, vel dictum dolor. Class aptent taciti sociosqu ad
        litora torquent per conubia nostra, per inceptos himenaeos. Suspendisse blandit eleifend
        diam, vel rutrum tellus vulputate quis. Aliquam eget libero aliquet, imperdiet nisl a,
        ornare ex. Sed rhoncus est ut libero porta lobortis. Fusce in dictum tellus.\n\n
        Suspendisse interdum ornare ante. Aliquam nec cursus lorem. Morbi id magna felis. Vivamus
        egestas, est a condimentum egestas, turpis nisl iaculis ipsum, in dictum tellus dolor sed
        neque. Morbi tellus erat, dapibus ut sem a, iaculis tincidunt dui. Interdum et malesuada
        fames ac ante ipsum primis in faucibus. Curabitur et eros porttitor, ultricies urna vitae,
        molestie nibh. Phasellus at commodo eros, non aliquet metus. Sed maximus nisl nec dolor
        bibendum, vel congue leo egestas.\n\n
        Sed interdum tortor nibh, in sagittis risus mollis quis. Curabitur mi odio, condimentum sit
        amet auctor at, mollis non turpis. Nullam pretium libero vestibulum, finibus orci vel,
        molestie quam. Fusce blandit tincidunt nulla, quis sollicitudin libero facilisis et. Integer
        interdum nunc ligula, et fermentum metus hendrerit id. Vestibulum lectus felis, dictum at
        lacinia sit amet, tristique id quam. Cras eu consequat dui. Suspendisse sodales nunc ligula,
        in lobortis sem porta sed. Integer id ultrices magna, in luctus elit. Sed a pellentesque
        est.\n\n
        Aenean nunc velit, lacinia sed dolor sed, ultrices viverra nulla. Etiam a venenatis nibh.
        Morbi laoreet, tortor sed facilisis varius, nibh orci rhoncus nulla, id elementum leo dui
        non lorem. Nam mollis ipsum quis auctor varius. Quisque elementum eu libero sed commodo. In
        eros nisl, imperdiet vel imperdiet et, scelerisque a mauris. Pellentesque varius ex nunc,
        quis imperdiet eros placerat ac. Duis finibus orci et est auctor tincidunt. Sed non viverra
        ipsum. Nunc quis augue egestas, cursus lorem at, molestie sem. Morbi a consectetur ipsum, a
        placerat diam. Etiam vulputate dignissim convallis. Integer faucibus mauris sit amet finibus
        convallis.\n\n
        Phasellus in aliquet mi. Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et
        malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. In volutpat arcu ut felis sagittis, in finibus massa
        gravida. Pellentesque id tellus orci. Integer dictum, lorem sed efficitur ullamcorper,
        libero justo consectetur ipsum, in mollis nisl ex sed nisl. Donec maximus ullamcorper
        sodales. Praesent bibendum rhoncus tellus nec feugiat. In a ornare nulla. Donec rhoncus
        libero vel nunc consequat, quis tincidunt nisl eleifend. Cras bibendum enim a justo luctus
        vestibulum. Fusce dictum libero quis erat maximus, vitae volutpat diam dignissim.
    </string>

    <string name="privacy_string">Neighbrsnook is a verified community. To keep your neighborhood safe we want to confirm you live here.</string>

</resources>